121912train
Annotation for intention:

Argumentation/Knowledge-Acquisition: why document/room/other #41 shouldn't be cleared/what happened to moving

Annotation for control:
Danny McCarty: Danny is the only sender of messages in this thread, and gives Pam Daily his argument about why 41 shouldn't be cleared, and asks her about moving.



<xml>

<message>



	<thread_id>121912</thread_id>



	<depth>0</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>725024</message_id>

	<to name="Pamela Daily" id="880" address="pdaily@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Danny McCarty" id="304" address="dmccarty@ENRON.COM"/>

	<cc name="Rod Hayslett" id="5425" address="rhaysle@ENRON.COM"/>



	<parent_id></parent_id>



	<subject>Furniture</subject>



	<date_time>2001-09-18 09:41:49</date_time>



	<content>

    

M1.1. Pam,

[Conventional: salutation]

M1.2. I don't see why the clearing of 41 is a prerequisite.

[Inform: Dan doesn't know why 41 must be cleared]

M1.3. Let's just get it moved from 4th to where ever so people can see it.

[Inform: they should move 41 (or its contents, if it is a room) to somewhere more visible]  

M1.4. I've got a whole floor of people apprehensive about the move and wasting time talking about what the working enviornment might be like when we finally move back.

[Inform: Dan knows many people who are unhappy about the move]

M1.5. We've got enough to worry about, this isn't worth the noise.

[Inform: Dan thinks this isn't worth all the noise that will ensue]

M1.6. If people just see it, they will understand that this is not going to be a minimum footprint sardine pack, and any noise will stop.

[Inform: if people see this, noise will end]

M1.7. When can we expect it to be available for viewing.

[Request-Information: when can 41 be available for viewing]

Flink1.7

M1.8. Do you want me to have Julie arrange it with Claudia?

[Request-Information: should Julie arrange this with Claudia]

Flink1.8

M1.9. Also, What has happened to our move?

[Request-Information: what happened to the move]

Flink1.9

M1.10. We were supposed to move yesterday, we're all packed up in boxes, and nobody seems to know what happened or when we are moving now.

[Inform: moving was supposed to occur yesterday, and nobody knows what happened]

M1.11. Dan

[Conventional: signature]



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>121912</thread_id>



	<depth>1</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>725028</message_id>

	<to name="Pamela Daily" id="880" address="pdaily@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Danny McCarty" id="304" address="dmccarty@ENRON.COM"/>



	<parent_id>725024</parent_id>



	<subject>Furniture</subject>



	<date_time>2001-09-19 10:36:08</date_time>



	<content>

    

M2.1. What about our move????

[Request-Information: what about move]

Flink2.1



	</content>

</message>

</xml>

Hierarchical Power Annotation: N/A
Person_1: 
Person_2: 
Reason: 

Situational Power Annotation: N/A
Person_1: 
Person_2: 
Reason: 

Attempt at Exercising Power Annotation: N/A
DFUs: 
Person_1:
Person_2:
Type:
Successful?:
Reason: 

Influence Annotation: N/A
Person_1:
Person_2:
Reason:

Attempt at Influence Annotation:
DFUs: M1.2-M1.6
Person_1: Danny McCarty
Person_2: Pamela Daily
Successful?: No Reply
Reason: In message 1, Danny gives Pam the reasons why he thinks clearing 41 is unnecessary.
