93
Annotation for intention:

Argumentation: whether to accept InterContinental Exchange offer/Greg Whalley's and Andy Zipper's opinions on it


Annotation for control:
John Sherriff: John initiates the thread and tells the others to accept the ICE offer.


<?xml version="1.0"?>



<!--

-

- Sequel Pro dump

- Version 155

- http://code.google.com/p/sequel-pro

-

- Host: 127.0.0.1 (MySQL 5.0.67)

- Database: enron

- Generation Time: 2008-12-01 15:18:53 -0500

-

-->



	<custom>

	<row>

		<thread_id>93</thread_id>

		<depth>0</depth>

		<type>ThreadNode</type>

		<message_id>292360</message_id>

	<to name="" id="15997" address="Boyd/Enron@EUEnronXGate"/>

	<to name="Justin Boyd" id="890" address="Justin.Boyd/Enron@EUEnronXGate"/>

	<from name="John Sherriff" id="4671" address="john.sherriff@enron.com"/>

	<cc name="Greg Whalley" id="27104" address="Greg.Whalley@ENRON.com"/>

	<cc name="" id="17221" address="Brown/Enron@EUEnronXGate"/>

	<cc name="Michael Brown" id="2202" address="Michael.Brown/Enron@EUEnronXGate"/>

	<cc name="Greg Piper" id="1665" address="Greg.Piper@ENRON.com"/>

	<cc name="Andy Zipper" id="5063" address="Andy.Zipper@ENRON.com"/>

	<to name="" id="4256" address="??SJustin.Boyd/Enron@EUEnronXGate"/>

	<from name="John Sherriff" id="4671" address="A177817E-7D75C390-8625653F-6307BB@ENRON.com"/>

	<cc name="Greg Whalley" id="27104" address="DA82494B-FC99BFE6-862565DA-5FA576@ENRON.com"/>

	<cc name="" id="4344" address="??SMichael.Brown/Enron@EUEnronXGate"/>

	<cc name="Greg Piper" id="1665" address="Gpiper@ENRON.com"/>

	<cc name="Andy Zipper" id="5063" address="azipper@enron.com"/>

		<parent_id>NULL</parent_id>

		<subject>Recommended Offer by ICE for IPE Holdings</subject>

		<date_time>2001-05-24 21:38:47</date_time>

		<content>

M1.1. My view is that we should go ahead and accept the ICE offer.

[Inform: John thinks they should accept the ICE offer]

M1.2. Please proceed with

the acceptance offer unless someone has a strong objection

[Inform: recipients should proceed with acceptance offer unless there is a strong objection]

M1.3. in which case let's

discuss on Tuesday. [Y]

[Inform: if there is an objection they will discuss this on Tuesday]



M1.4. John

[Conventional: signature]



</content>

	</row>

	<row>

		<thread_id>93</thread_id>

		<depth>1</depth>

		<type>ThreadNode</type>

		<message_id>292204</message_id>

	<to name="John Sherriff" id="4671" address="john.sherriff@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Greg Piper" id="1665" address="Greg.Piper@ENRON.com"/>

	<to name="John Sherriff" id="4671" address="A177817E-7D75C390-8625653F-6307BB@ENRON.com"/>

	<from name="Greg Piper" id="1665" address="Gpiper@ENRON.com"/>

		<parent_id>292360</parent_id>

		<subject>Clearing discussion</subject>

		<date_time>2001-05-25 16:17:03</date_time>

		<content>

M2.1. I heard Whalley was neutral to the London Clearing thing.

[Inform: Greg Piper heard Greg Whalley was neutral to a London Clearing thing]



M2.2. My take on it is that we want both the trade and the information associated with it like who it was, etc.

[Inform: Greg Piper's take is that they want both the trade and associated info]

M2.3. In theory, that is true.

M2.4. The question is that in reality, is that sustainable.

[Inform: not sure that this is sustainable, though in theory this is true]

M2.5. In gas and power U. S., other than ICE we are able to do that for the most part.

[Inform: other than ICE, in gas and power US, they were able to do this for the most part]



M2.6. Andy Zipper had a good idea and is focusing on a subset of this which is finding a way for hedge funds, institutions and locals to get at our liquidity through a clearing agent.

[Inform: Andy Zipper's good idea and how he is acting upon it]

M2.7. These entities do not transact currently on EnronOnline because of credit restrictions

M2.8. so if we could set up a master user, like a clearing agent, then the agent would set up sub users like the funds and/or locals.

[Inform: entities Zipper is focusing on are not currently able to transact on EnronOnline, so a clearing agent should be set up]

M2.9. This should not effect Whalley's concern

M2.10. because all these trades, though anonymous, would be incremental.

[Inform: this should not affect Whalley's concern, because trades would be incremental]



M2.11. Your thoughts?

[Request-Information: any thoughts]

Flink2.11



M2.12. GP

[Conventional: signature]



</content>

	</row>

	</custom>

Hierarchical Power Annotation: N/A
Person_1: 
Person_2: 
Reason: 

Situational Power Annotation:
Person_1: John Sherriff
Person_2: Greg Piper, CC(1)
Reason: In M1.2-M1.3 John tells the others to accept an offer or tell him why they shouldn't.

Attempt at Exercising Power Annotation:
DFUs: M1.2-M1.3
Person_1: John Sherriff
Person_2: Greg Piper, CC(1)
Type: Situational
Successful?: N
Reason: After John tells the others to accept an offer or tell him why they shouldn't in message 1, Greg gives John thoughts in message 2 but doesn't seem to be set one way or the other. 

Influence Annotation:
Person_1: Andy Zipper
Person_2: Greg Piper
Reason: Greg Piper calls Andy's idea good in M2.6, showing that Andy has credibility and that his idea was picked up on by at least one other person. 

Attempt at Influence Annotation:
DFUs: M1.1
Person_1: John Sherriff
Person_2: Greg Piper
Successful?: N
Reason: After John tells Greg and the other recipients of message 1 that they should accept the ICE offer, Greg doesn't seem to be 100% sold on it in message 2.
