<xml>

<message>



	<thread_id>142489</thread_id>



	<depth>0</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>1118651</message_id>

	<to name="Shelley Corman" id="102777" address="Shelley.Corman@ENRON.com"/>

	<from name="Rick Dietz" id="4682" address="rick.dietz@kingwoodcable.com"/>

	<cc name="Alma Carrillo" id="5389" address="Alma.Carrillo@ENRON.com"/>

	<to name="Shelley Corman" id="102777" address="scorman@enron.com"/>

	<cc name="Alma Carrillo" id="5389" address="Acarril@ENRON.com"/>



	<parent_id></parent_id>



	<subject>Out of Office - Monday morning</subject>



	<date_time>2001-10-28 21:32:41</date_time>



	<content>

    

M1.1. Shelley,

[Conventional: signature]

M1.2. I will be out of the office tomorrow morning participating in a charity golf tournament sponsored by EDS at South Shore Harbor.

[Inform: Rick will be out of the office tomorrow to play in a charity golf tournament]

M1.3. Mark Giglotti, Jeannie Licciardo, Don Stacy and I are playing together.

[Inform: three others who are also playing]

M1.4. I know the timing may be bad because of the financial project we have been preparing but the charitable contribution to play was quite generous and I do not want to back out of my commitment to the other team members.

[Inform: despite bad timing, Rick made a commitment to team, and charitable contribution is significant]

M1.5. HOWEVER, IF YOU NEED ME FOR ANY REASON, PLEASE PAGE ME AT 1(800) 609-6967 OR CALL MY CELL PHONE AT (713) 569-4140.

[Inform: pager and cell numbers, if Shelley needs to contact Rick]

M1.6. ALMA WILL ALSO KNOW HOW TO GET A HOLD OF ME.

[Inform: Alma will also know how to get in touch with Rick]

M1.7. I will only be 45 minutes away and will be able to come straight into the office, if needed.

[Inform: Rick will only be 45 minutes away and can come into the office if necessary]

M1.8. I will check in during the day with Linda Trevino, as she will be sitting in for me at your staff meeting.

[Inform: Rick will check in with Linda, who will sit in for Rick at the staff meeting]

M1.9. Rick

[Conventional: signature]



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>142489</thread_id>



	<depth>1</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>1120078</message_id>

	<to name="Rick Dietz" id="4682" address="rick.dietz@kingwoodcable.com"/>

	<from name="Shelley Corman" id="102777" address="scorman@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id>1118651</parent_id>



	<subject>Out of Office - Monday morning</subject>



	<date_time>2001-10-28 22:18:04</date_time>



	<content>

    

M2.1. Rick

[Conventional: salutation]

M2.2. I have a number of contracts that the bankers want early tomorrow.

[Inform: Shelley has some contracts that bankers want early tomorrow]

Sflink2.2

M2.3. I am assuming Elizabeth will be in to help me?

[Request-Information: will Elizabeth be in to help Shelley]

Flink2.3



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>142489</thread_id>



	<depth>2</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>1118647</message_id>

	<to name="Shelley Corman" id="102777" address="Shelley.Corman@ENRON.com"/>

	<from name="Rick Dietz" id="4682" address="rick.dietz@kingwoodcable.com"/>

	<to name="Shelley Corman" id="102777" address="scorman@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id>1120078</parent_id>



	<subject>Out of Office - Monday morning</subject>



	<date_time>2001-10-28 23:27:30</date_time>



	<content>

    

M3.1. Elizabeth will be in.

[Inform: Elizabeth will be in]

Blink2.3

M3.2. Also, Linda Trevino will be in the office.

[Inform: Linda will also be in]

M3.3. All

contracts are in Envision as well as in the file room on 39.

[Inform: locations of contracts]

Blink2.2

M3.4. If you need me to be there, just let me know.

[Inform: Shelley should tell Rick if she needs him to be there]



	</content>

</message>

</xml>