<custom>

	<row>

		<thread_id>94</thread_id>

		<depth>0</depth>

		<type>ThreadNode</type>

		<message_id>292543</message_id>

	<to name="Andy Zipper" id="5063" address="Andy.Zipper@ENRON.com"/>

	<from name="Daniel Diamond" id="2854" address="Dan.Diamond@ENRON.com"/>

	<cc name="Jay Webb" id="52818" address="Jay.Webb@ENRON.com"/>

	<cc name="Kal Shah" id="199" address="Kal.Shah@ENRON.com"/>

	<to name="Andy Zipper" id="5063" address="azipper@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Daniel Diamond" id="27465" address="Ddiamon@ENRON.com"/>

	<cc name="Jay Webb" id="52818" address="Jwebb@ENRON.com"/>

	<cc name="Kal Shah" id="199" address="Kshah@ENRON.com"/>

		<parent_id>NULL</parent_id>

		<subject>EOL Email</subject>

		<date_time>2001-05-24 09:34:15</date_time>

		<content>

M1.1. Andy,

[Conventional: salutation]

M1.2. I know EOL email is far down on the priority list

M1.3. but I wanted to forward the responses to you.

[Inform: though EOL email is low on priority list, Dan is forwarding companies' responses]

M1.4. Just about everyone we spoke with gave a positive response.

M1.5. It looks like our biggest hurdle is getting them to actually complete the information and not just ignore it.

[Inform: most companies gave a positive response/biggest concern is getting them to fill out info and not ignore it]

M1.6. If we ever went forward with this,

M1.7. I would suggest that we use pop up boxes first

M1.8. and then forward a list of the remaining names that we need to the Master User to fill out.

[Inform: Dan's suggestion is to use pop-up boxes and then forward a list of the remaining names to the Master User to fill out]

M1.9. -Dan

[Conventional: signature]

M1.10. Here is a list of the companies and their responses about receiving email updates from EOL:

M1.11. Company					Response

Kansas City Power &amp; Light			No problem asking for the information as long as it is strictly for our use

Central Hudson Gas &amp; Electric Co.		&quot;

Cline Resources &amp; Development Co.		&quot;

Duke						Sounds great

Vitol						Sounds fine

Coastal						Perfect

Koch						Preferable

BP Canada					No problem with it

Chevron Canada					Would fill out the information

Engage Canada					Said that about 50% of the traders would take the time to give us the info.

TransCanada					They would fill it out

SaskEnergy Inc.				Not too excited about the deal but would consider it

Burlington Resources				Master User actually responded by sending a full list of user names, ids, emails and what they trade.

Unocal						Felt if we sent out a pop up survey about half of his traders would fill in the info.

CMS						Thought most traders would ignore a survey as they feel Enron has too much information about them already.  However, if 						we sent the Master User a form that would assist in a higher level of customer service, he would fill out the information.

BP Amoco					Felt most traders would ignore a survey unless they were forced to fill it out

[Inform: chart listing companies and their responses to receiving email updates from EnronOnline]



</content>

	</row>

	<row>

		<thread_id>94</thread_id>

		<depth>2</depth>

		<type>ThreadNode</type>

		<message_id>292567</message_id>

	<to name="Andy Zipper" id="5063" address="Andy.Zipper@ENRON.com"/>

	<from name="Daniel Diamond" id="2854" address="Dan.Diamond@ENRON.com"/>

	<to name="Andy Zipper" id="5063" address="azipper@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Daniel Diamond" id="27465" address="Ddiamon@ENRON.com"/>

		<parent_id>NULL</parent_id>

		<subject>EOL Email</subject>

		<date_time>2001-06-05 09:05:55</date_time>

		<content>

M2.1. Mark Greenberg is trying to get back in touch with their attorney.

M2.2. I called Alan Kurzer Thursday and Mark called their attorney Friday.

[Inform: Mark Greenberg and Dan are trying to get in touch with someone's (Kurzer's?) attorney]

M2.3. We're still waiting on a response to the renegotiated definitive agreement.

[Inform: still waiting to hear a response to renegotiated definitive agreement]

M2.4. Once that is finalized (should be any day now), it goes up to the parent for final approval.

[Inform: once finalized, this renegotiated agreement goes to the parent for final approval]

M2.5. -Dan

[Conventional: signature]



</content>

	</row>

	</custom>