<xml>

<message>



	<thread_id>35471</thread_id>



	<depth>0</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>21948</message_id>

	<to name="Kenneth Lay" id="40164" address="Kenneth.Lay@ENRON.com"/>

	<from name="Michael S Telle" id="67913" address="mtelle@velaw.com"/>

	<cc name="John Watson" id="59838" address="jwatson@velaw.com"/>



	<parent_id></parent_id>



	<subject>Referendum Campaign</subject>



	<date_time>2000-10-02 06:18:00</date_time>



	<content>

    

M1.1. Mr. Lay--

[Conventional: salutation]

M1.2. During the negotiations with the Rockets as to how much each party would

contribute to the Arena referendum campaign, Mike Goldberg of Baker & Botts

suggested that the Rockets would like to net their contribution obligation

against other contributions that they solicited.

[Inform: Mike Goldberg's suggestion during negotiations with the Rockets]

M1.3. After a conversation with you, John Watson and I advised Mike Goldberg that

you did not want to be competing with the Rockets in soliciting

contributions to the Arena referendum campaign.

[Inform: John Watson and sender's advisement to Mike after talking to Ken Lay]

M1.4. Mike Goldberg called Friday and asked whether it would be acceptable for the

Rockets to net against their contribution obligation contributions that they

have solicited from Baker & Botts, Jim MacInvale and Tilman Fertitta.

[Inform: Mike Goldberg's request for permission on behalf of the Rockets when he called Friday]

M1.5. Mike

suggested that these three persons would be the only outside persons that

would be solicited by the Rockets.

[Inform: Mike's belief that Baker & Botts, Jim McInvale, and Tilman Fertitta are only entities that the Rockets would solicit]

M1.6. Would you please let me know if this is acceptable to you. [Y]

[Request-Information: whether the above is acceptable to Ken Lay]

Flink1.6

M1.7. You or Rosalee

may call me at 713-758-2350 or send me a response e-mail at

mtelle@velaw.com.

[Inform: Ken Lay or Rosalee can call Michael at phone number provided or email at address provided]

M1.8. Sincerely,

[Conventional: (beginning of a) signature]



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>35471</thread_id>



	<depth>1</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>21949</message_id>

	<to name="Michael S Telle" id="67913" address="mtelle@velaw.com"/>

	<from name="Rosalee Fleming" id="40264" address="Rosalee.Fleming@ENRON.com"/>



	<parent_id>21948</parent_id>



	<subject>Referendum Campaign</subject>



	<date_time>2000-10-02 06:27:00</date_time>



	<content>

    

M2.1. Hi Michael -

[Conventional: salutation]

M2.2. Mr. Lay is returning from his trip today.

M2.3. He will be in the office tomorrow.

[Inform: Ken Lay is returning from a trip today and will be in the office tomorrow]



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>35471</thread_id>



	<depth>2</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>22001</message_id>

	<to name="Michael S Telle" id="67913" address="mtelle@velaw.com"/>

	<from name="Rosalee Fleming" id="40264" address="Rosalee.Fleming@ENRON.com"/>



	<parent_id>21949</parent_id>



	<subject>Referendum Campaign</subject>



	<date_time>2000-10-04 14:45:00</date_time>



	<content>

    

M3.1. Michael -

[Conventional: salutation]

M3.2. Ken Lay said to tell you this is fine.

[Inform: Ken Lay grants permission to Mike Goldberg]

Blink1.6



	</content>

</message>

</xml>