<xml>

<message>



	<thread_id>127941</thread_id>



	<depth>0</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>763333</message_id>

	<to name="Sara Shackleton" id="64528" address="sshackl@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Kim S Ward" id="18442" address="kward@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id></parent_id>



	<subject>City of Glendale</subject>



	<date_time>2001-10-05 14:59:07</date_time>



	<content>

    

M1.1. Sara,

[Conventional: salutation]

M1.2. Believe it or not, we are very close getting our signed ISDA from the City of Glendale.

[Inform: Kim et al. are getting close to getting a signed ISDA from the City of Glendale]

M1.3. Steve Lins, the City attorney had a couple of questions which I will attempt to relay without having a copy of the documents.

[Inform: Steve Lins, the City attorney, had some questions, which Kim is attempting to relay]

M1.4. 1)  I am assuming that he obtained a for legal opinion letter or document of some sort.

M1.5. This document references a confirmation and we are not sure what this references.

M1.6. Typically, it references a transaction, which in this case, there are no transactions yet.

M1.7. He feels this reference should be deleted.

[Inform: Steve Lins thinks an unclear reference should be deleted from a document]

M1.8. What is your opinion regarding this?

[Request-Information: Sara's opinion on this]

Flink1.8

M1.9. 2)  We sent him a couple of form documents to facilitate the documents required under the ISDA.

M1.10. One form ws a form resolution.

M1.11. They have already received City Council approval to enter into financial tranactions and to enter into an ISDA with us.

M1.12. Steve is going to get a certified copy of this Resolution.

[Inform: Kim et al. sent Steve Lins some form documents to facilitate documents required under the ISDA, including a form resolution, of which Steve is going to get a certified copy, since they already have City Council approval]

M1.13. Will this suffice?

[Request-Information: is this good enough]

Flink1.13

M1.14. When you return, I may try to do one last conference call to alleviate any unanswered questions.

[Inform: when Sara returns, Kim may attempt one more conference call to resolve her unanswered questions]

M1.15. I think we will have an executed ISDA with the City of Glendale by the end of next week.

M1.16. I am going to be out there meeting with them on Wednesday.

[Inform: Kim thinks they will get an executed ISDA with Glendale by the end of next week, and she will be there to meet with officials on Wednesday]

M1.17. Thanks for your help,

[Conventional: thanks]



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>127941</thread_id>



	<depth>1</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>874438</message_id>

	<to name="Kim S Ward" id="18442" address="Kim.Ward@ENRON.com"/>

	<from name="Sara Shackleton" id="64528" address="Sara.Shackleton@ENRON.com"/>

	<cc name="Marie Heard" id="40104" address="Marie.Heard@ENRON.com"/>

	<to name="Kim S Ward" id="18442" address="kward@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Sara Shackleton" id="64528" address="sshackl@enron.com"/>

	<cc name="Marie Heard" id="40104" address="Mheard@ENRON.com"/>



	<parent_id>763333</parent_id>



	<subject>City of Glendale</subject>



	<date_time>2001-10-08 09:02:56</date_time>



	<content>

    

M2.1. Kim:

[Conventional: salutation]

M2.2. Can you obtain the name of Glendale's bond counsel (lawyer's name, phone number, email, etc.)? [Y]

[Request-Information: name, number, and email of Glendale's bond counsel]

Flink2.2

M2.3. Thanks.

[Conventional: thanks]

M2.4. SS

[Conventional: signature]



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>127941</thread_id>



	<depth>2</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>763334</message_id>

	<to name="Sara Shackleton" id="64528" address="sshackl@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Kim S Ward" id="18442" address="kward@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id>874438</parent_id>



	<subject>City of Glendale</subject>



	<date_time>2001-10-08 09:26:50</date_time>



	<content>

    

M3.1. Glendale's City Attorney is Steve Lins.

M3.2. His phone number is 818-548-2080 and his email is slins@ci.glendale.ca.us.

[Inform: name, number, and email of Glendale's City Attorney]

Blink2.2

Sflink3.2

M3.3. Please let me know if you need anything else.

[Inform: Sara should let Kim know if she needs anything else]

M3.4. I will be in their offices on Wednesday.

[Inform: Kim will be in Glendale's offices on Wednesday]



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>127941</thread_id>



	<depth>2</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>874028</message_id>

	<to name="Sara Shackleton" id="64528" address="sshackl@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Marie Heard" id="40104" address="Mheard@ENRON.com"/>



	<parent_id>874438</parent_id>



	<subject>City of Glendale</subject>



	<date_time>2001-10-08 10:15:27</date_time>



	<content>



M4.1. Sara:

[Conventional: salutation]

M4.2. I do not see a copy of an opinion in the file nor have we received one since I sent the execution copies of the ISDA to Steve Lins.

[Inform: Marie doesn't see a copy of an opinion in file and has not received one since sending execution copies of ISDA to Steve Lins]



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>127941</thread_id>



	<depth>2</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>763337</message_id>

	<to name="slins@ci.glendale.ca.us" id="106187" address="slins@ci.glendale.ca.us"/>

	<from name="Kim S Ward" id="18442" address="kward@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id>874438</parent_id>



	<subject>City of Glendale</subject>



	<date_time>2001-10-08 16:18:22</date_time>



	<content>

    

M5.1. Steve,

[Conventional: salutation]

M5.2. could you provide the name, phone number, etc. of your bond council for our attorney, Sara Shackleton? [Y]

[Request-Information: name and contact information of bond counsel for Sara]

Blink2.2

Flink5.2

M5.3. Thanks,

[Conventional: thanks]



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>127941</thread_id>



	<depth>3</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>1117626</message_id>

	<to name="Kim S Ward" id="18442" address="kward@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Sara Shackleton" id="64528" address="sshackl@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id>763334</parent_id>



	<subject>City of Glendale</subject>



	<date_time>2001-10-08 09:27:29</date_time>



	<content>

    

M6.1. I need the city's bond counsel (outside counsel). [Y]

[Inform: Sara needs city's bond counsel's information, not city attorney's information]

Blink3.2

Sflink6.1



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>127941</thread_id>



	<depth>4</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>763335</message_id>

	<to name="Sara Shackleton" id="64528" address="sshackl@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Kim S Ward" id="18442" address="kward@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id>1117626</parent_id>



	<subject>City of Glendale</subject>



	<date_time>2001-10-08 10:03:53</date_time>



	<content>

    

M7.1. Is this to obtain outside opinion?

[Request-Information: is this to get outside opinion]

Blink6.1

Flink7.1

M7.2. I thought we were going to do that at our own expense.

[Inform: Kim thought this was to be at their own expense]

Sflink7.2



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>127941</thread_id>



	<depth>5</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>763443</message_id>

	<to name="Kim S Ward" id="18442" address="Kim.Ward@ENRON.com"/>

	<from name="Sara Shackleton" id="64528" address="Sara.Shackleton@ENRON.com"/>

	<to name="Kim S Ward" id="18442" address="kward@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Sara Shackleton" id="64528" address="sshackl@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id>763335</parent_id>



	<subject>City of Glendale</subject>



	<date_time>2001-10-08 10:38:46</date_time>



	<content>

    

M8.1. We are going to do this at our own expense.

[Inform: this will be at Sara's and others' own expense]

Blink7.2

M8.2. But we would like to hire Glendale's bond counsel.

[Inform: Sara et al. would like to hire Glendale's bond counsel]

M8.3. I don't know the name of Glendale's bond counsel or how to get in touch with them.

[Inform: Sara doesn't know bond counsel's name or contact information]

Sflink8.3



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>127941</thread_id>



	<depth>6</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>763336</message_id>

	<to name="Sara Shackleton" id="64528" address="sshackl@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Kim S Ward" id="18442" address="kward@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id>763443</parent_id>



	<subject>City of Glendale</subject>



	<date_time>2001-10-08 11:43:20</date_time>



	<content>

    

M9.1. I will work on this for you - and will be in touch.

[Inform: Kim will find out information about bond counsel for Sara]

Blink8.3

M9.2. Thanks!

[Conventional: thanks]



	</content>

</message>

</xml>