<custom>

	<row>

		<thread_id>68</thread_id>

		<depth>0</depth>

		<type>ThreadNode</type>

		<message_id>276677</message_id>

	<to name="James Derrick Jr" id="51608" address="James.Derrick@ENRON.com"/>

	<from name="Paul Pien" id="92291" address="ppien@elawforum.com"/>

	<cc name="John Henry" id="56305" address="jhenry@elawforum.com"/>

	<cc name="Steve Wyatt" id="102409" address="sbwoil@aol.com"/>

	<to name="James Derrick Jr" id="51608" address="jderric@enron.com"/>

		<parent_id>NULL</parent_id>

		<subject>Registration of Enron Corp. on the eLawForum Web Site</subject>

		<date_time>2001-05-21 18:04:25</date_time>

		<content>

M1.1. James,

[Conventional: salutation]



M1.2. Per Steve Wyatt's suggestion, I have taken the liberty of registering Enron

Corporation on the eLawForum web site.

M1.3. In the course of completing the

registration, I accepted the eLawForum User Agreement on behalf of Enron.

[Inform: registered Enron on the eLawForum website/accepted User Agreement on Enron's behalf]

Sflink1.3

M1.4. Please let me know if you have any questions about the User Agreement.

[Request-Information: any questions about User Agreement]

Flink1.4

M1.5. We would be happy to address any concerns.

[Inform: would be happy to address any concerns]



M1.6. I have created the 2 roles for you that are required to use our site.

M1.7. The

first role is as &quot;Client Administrator.&quot;

M1.8. This role allows you to manage the

site, primarily by adding and deleting users and assigning them appropriate

roles.

M1.9. Your login name and password for your roles as Client Administrator

are: Login - &quot;jderrick&quot; and Password - &quot;enron&quot;.

M1.10. Please note that both your

login and passwords are case sensitive.

[Inform: created 2 roles required for using this site/first is Client Administrator/explains this role/gives user name and password]



M1.11. I have also created for you the second role of &quot;RFP Administrator.&quot;  M1.12. In this

role, you can create a new RFP and/or manage existing RFPs.

M1.13. You are

required to have a second Login name and Password for this second role.

M1.14. I

have assigned you the Login in of &quot;jamesderrick&quot; and Password of &quot;enroncorp&quot;

in your role as RFP Administrator.

M1.15. Once again, the login name and password

are case sensitive.

[Inform: second role is RFP administrator/Paul Pien explains this role/gives a second user name and password]



M1.16. To logon and begin using the web site, go to www.elawforum.com.

M1.17. Click on

&quot;logon&quot; and sign on in your role as RFP Administrator.

[Inform: log-on instructions]

M1.18. Let me know if you

would like a quick walk through the site.

[Request-Information: let Paul know if Jim would like a walk-through of the site]

Flink1.18

M1.19. In addition, please contact me

when you are ready to post your first RFP. [Y]

[Request-Information: contact Paul when ready to post the first RFP]

Flink1.19

M1.20. Our service includes providing

Enron hands on assistance every step of the way.

[Inform: Enron is entitled to hands-on assistance whenever it is needed]



M1.21. Sincerely,





M1.22. Paul Pien

M1.23. Vice President

M1.24. eLawForum

M1.25. 1250 24th Street, NW, Suite 350

M1.26. Washington, DC  20037

M1.27. Work: 202-466-0520

M1.28. Fax: 202-466-0583

M1.29. ppien@elawforum.com

M1.30. www.elawforum.com

[Conventional: signature and contact information]





</content>

	</row>

	<row>

		<thread_id>68</thread_id>

		<depth>1</depth>

		<type>ThreadNodeBubble</type>

		<message_id>2000022</message_id>

		<parent_id>276677</parent_id>

		<subject>Registration of Enron Corp. on the eLawForum Web Site</subject>

		<date_time>2001-05-22 05:10:24</date_time>

		<content>



M2.1. Thank you for the message.

[Conventional: thanks]

M2.2. Please note for your records, however, that neither I nor Enron has accepted the eLawForum User Agreement and that we have not authorized any individual or entity to accept it on our behalf.

[Inform: neither Enron nor Jim Derrick has accepted eLawForum's User Agreement nor authorized anyone else to accept it on their behalf]

Blink1.3

M2.3. Jim Derrick

[Conventional: signature]



</content>

	</row>

	</custom>