<xml>

<message>



	<thread_id>6098</thread_id>



	<depth>0</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>1187590</message_id>

	<to name="Justin Boyd" id="890" address="justin.boyd@enron.com"/>

	<to name="Edmund Cooper" id="36383" address="edmund.cooper@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Michael E Taylor" id="75886" address="Mark.E.Taylor@ENRON.com"/>



	<parent_id></parent_id>



	<subject>Local Counsel Questions</subject>



	<date_time>1999-09-30 14:52:00</date_time>



	<content>

    

M1.1. Can you guys please send over a copy of the questions that were submitted to

local counsel in Europe relating to the online trading project? [Y]

[Request-Information: a copy of questions about online trading project sent to Europe]

Flink1.1

M1.2. Alan needs

it for Australia and Louise has asked me to deal with Columbia.

[Inform: Alan needs a copy for Australia, and Mark needs one for Colombia]

M1.3. Thanks,

[Conventional: thanks]



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>6098</thread_id>



	<depth>1</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>1187591</message_id>

	<to name="Michael E Taylor" id="75886" address="Mark.E.Taylor@ENRON.com"/>

	<to name="David Minns" id="2940" address="david.minns@enron.com"/>

	<to name="Alan Aronowitz" id="3611" address="Alan.Aronowitz@ENRON.com"/>

	<from name="Edmund Cooper" id="36383" address="edmund.cooper@enron.com"/>

	<cc name="Justin Boyd" id="890" address="justin.boyd@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id>1187590</parent_id>



	<subject>Local Counsel Questions</subject>



	<date_time>1999-10-01 05:18:00</date_time>



	<content>

    

M2.1. Dear All,

[Conventional: salutation]

M2.2. Following Mark's and David's request for the due diligence questionnaires

that we have used in Europe for EOL, I am pleased to attach the following:

[Inform: following Mark's and David's request for questionnaires, Edmund is attaching the following]

Blink1.1

M2.3. 1. Questionnaire regarding internet trading

M2.4. 2. Questionnaire regarding commodity derivatives trading

[Inform: two attached files are questionnaire regarding internet trading, and questionnaire regarding commodity derivatives trading]

M2.5. A couple of points I'd like to make:

[Inform: the following are some points Edmund would like to make]

M2.6. - the internet questionnaire refers to the European Economic Area "passport"

(entitling you to trade in one EEA country by vitue of being regulated by

another EEA country).

M2.7. Obviously this is not appropriate for S. America or

Oceania and Asia.

[Inform: internet questionnaire refers to European Economic Area passport, which is inappropriate for South America, Oceania, or Asia]

M2.8. It is possible that you have some similar mechanism.

[Inform: it is possible that recipients have a similar mechanism]

M2.9. - the energy commodity questionnaire considers commodity derivatives trading.

[Inform: energy commodity questionnaire considers commodity derivatives trading]

M2.10. This questionniare was only sent to local counsel in jurisdictions for which

we had not already undertaken derivatives due diligence.

[Inform: questionnaire was only sent to jurisdictions where derivatives due diligence had not already been undertaken]

M2.11. In respect of

physical commodity trading, based on the due diligence we have done to date

in Europe, we have not undertaken any further due diligence for trading via

EOL.

[Inform: Edmund et al. have not undertaken further due diligence for trading via Enron Online]

M2.12. If you feel that you need to undertake any physical trading due

diligence, we have a set of questionnaires which I would be happy to pass on

to you to use as you see fit.

[Inform: if recipients need to undertake physical trading due diligence, Edmund will send more questionnaires]

M2.13. Please feel free to contact me if you have any queries or questions about any

of the above -

[Inform: recipients should contact Edmund if they have any questions]

M2.14. otherwise, happy hunting!

[Conventional: happy hunting]



	</content>

</message>

</xml>