<xml>

<message>



	<thread_id>50721</thread_id>



	<depth>0</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>165113</message_id>

	<to name="rmp@cpuc.ca.gov" id="91931" address="rmp@cpuc.ca.gov"/>

	<to name="rick.counihan@greenmountain.com" id="25017" address="rick.counihan@greenmountain.com"/>

	<to name="Jeff Dasovich" id="27095" address="Jeff.Dasovich@ENRON.com"/>

	<to name="burkee@cts.com" id="17888" address="burkee@cts.com"/>

	<to name="alexanms@sce.com" id="7202" address="alexanms@sce.com"/>

	<to name="craigc@calpine.com" id="25349" address="craigc@calpine.com"/>

	<to name="cushnice@sce.com" id="26222" address="cushnice@sce.com"/>

	<to name="Jeff Dasovich" id="28265" address="jdasovic@enron.com"/>

	<to name="Mike Day" id="78792" address="mday@gmssr.com"/>

	<to name="paulamirault@aec.ca" id="8123" address="paulamirault@aec.ca"/>

	<to name="porterdk@sce.com" id="34228" address="porterdk@sce.com"/>

	<to name="tomb@crossborderenergy.com" id="114784" address="tomb@crossborderenergy.com"/>

	<to name="lindseyhowdowning@dwt.com" id="72005" address="lindseyhowdowning@dwt.com"/>

	<to name="phildavies@aec.ca" id="91025" address="PhilDavies@aec.ca"/>

	<to name="jleslie@luce.com" id="57632" address="jleslie@luce.com"/>

	<to name="Transwestern Jeff Fawcett" id="55712" address="jfawcett@enron.com"/>

	<to name="rochmanm@spurr.org" id="98731" address="rochmanm@spurr.org"/>

	<to name="rick.counihan@greenmountain.com" id="25017" address="counihan@greenmountain.com"/>

	<to name="david.bayless@utility.com" id="28566" address="david.bayless@utility.com"/>

	<to name="bdingwall@unitedgas.com" id="12715" address="bdingwall@unitedgas.com"/>

	<to name="eke@aelaw.com" id="37332" address="eke@aelaw.com"/>

	<to name="Johnson_Pamela@lacoe.edu" id="60099" address="johnson_pamela@lacoe.edu"/>

	<to name="chj@aelaw.com" id="21980" address="chj@aelaw.com"/>

	<to name="karpjos@sf.whitecase.com" id="57264" address="karpjos@sf.whitecase.com"/>

	<to name="Keith McCrea" id="67587" address="kmccrea@sablaw.com"/>

	<to name="Joe@Dynegy Paul" id="2247" address="6266273191@messaging.sprintpcs.com"/>

	<to name="Susan M Scott" id="16810" address="sscott3@enron.com"/>

	<to name="gworster@txuenergy.com" id="46810" address="gworster@txuenergy.com"/>

	<to name="Gillian Wright" id="46816" address="gwright@sempra.com"/>

	<to name="Glen J Sullivan" id="46436" address="gsullivan@sempra.com"/>

	<to name="Zenee G Angeles" id="121377" address="ZAngeles@sempra.com"/>

	<from name="Mike Day" id="78792" address="mday@gmssr.com"/>



	<parent_id></parent_id>



	<subject>Report on meeting with Comm. Bilas re GIR Proposed Decision</subject>



	<date_time>2000-12-06 10:41:00</date_time>



	<content>

    

M1.1. This communication is intended for signatories of the Comprehensive

Settlement Agreement, and is confidential under Rule 51 of the Commission's

Rules of Practice and Procedure.

[Inform: whom this communication is intended for, and declaration of its confidentiality]

M1.2. Please do not forward this e-mail to other

parties. [Y]

[Inform: this email should not be forwarded to other people]

M1.3. During a meeting with Comm. Bilas today, he confirmed what we had been

previously advised, namely:

M1.4. He did not communicate with any of his

colleagues regarding the PD, he is very disappointed at the limited scope of

the PD, and knows it does not go as far as it should; he would support an

alternate offered by another commission which adopted more or all of the

CSA.

M1.5. He strongly urges parties to take their concerns about the PD to the

other commissioners.

M1.6. He acknowledges it will be a tough sell.

[Inform: what Comm. Bilas confirmed today, that Mike et al. had been previously advised]

M1.7. However, he

does not have any communication from the Democratic commissioners on this

issue either way, so he cannot predict their reaction with any certainty.

[Inform: Comm. Bilas cannot predict Democratic commissioners' reaction on the issue, since he has no communication from them]

M1.8. The main reason for his issuance of the PD in this form appears to be that

he felt that a more aggressive PD issued by a Wilson appointee would attract

attacks simply because it was not offered by the new commissioner.

[Inform: why Bilas issued the PD in a particular form]

M1.9. Additional data points:

[Inform: the following are additional points]

M1.10. Other key CPUC staff with access to President Lynch

that I spoke with today urged us to meet with her, and to emphasize that the

CSA does not result in a reduction in CPUC jurisdiction or regulatory

control (like AB 1890 did) and to take our best shot at convincing her and

Comm. Wood that customers, including core customers, may far much worse

under the interim than under the CSA (particularly in view of the interstate

capacity issues--as described by Mark Pocta of ORA on our recent conf.

call).

M1.11. In addition, a fourth Commissioner (who will be around to vote next

year) suggested similar tactics and offered support for such an effort.

[Inform: what other CPUC staff and a fourth Commissioner suggested]

M1.12. In light of this information, I suggest that we proceed to issue the letter

as planned, and ask that all parties, including SoCalGas, quickly review the

next draft to see if they can sign on.

M1.13. We would like to have as many of the

CSA signatories as possible on the letter.

M1.14. I hope to get the new draft out

today or early tomorrow.

[Inform: Mike would like all parties to review a letter draft and sign it if possible, so he can send it out ASAP]

M1.15. Please respond by COB Thursday or early on Friday. [Y]

[Request-Action: respond by close of business on Thursday or early Friday]

Flink1.15

M1.16. Next, I have asked for a meeting with Pres. Lynch.

M1.17. I would like other

parties to attend as well (or schedule their own meetings). [Y]

M1.18. As soon as I

get a date, I will advise.

[Inform: Mike has asked for a meeting with President Lynch, and after he gets a date, he will let other people know, so they can attend also or schedule their own meetings]

M1.19. Bottom line:  We urge parties to sign the letter and to file comments

supporting adoption of the CSA.

M1.20. We need to meet with Lynch, and until and

unless we get a firm "no", we should not assume the settlement is dead.

[Inform: everyone should sign the previously mentioned letter and assume settlement regarding CSA is still possible]

M1.21. We

should file comments on the PD on Monday which at least list our objections

to the PD and open the door for discussions on how to revive the CSA.

[Inform: Mike's suggestion to file comments that list objections to PD and encourage revival of the CSA]

M1.22. If possible, we will try to arrange a conference call on Friday.

[Inform: Mike et al. will try to arrange a conference call on Friday]

M1.23. Please call if you have any questions.

[Inform: recipients should call if they have questions]

M1.24. Mike Day

[Conventional: signature]



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>50721</thread_id>



	<depth>2</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>165183</message_id>

	<to name="Alan Comnes" id="836" address="acomnes@enron.com"/>

	<from name="Mike Day" id="78792" address="mday@gmssr.com"/>

	<cc name="Jeff Dasovich" id="28265" address="jdasovic@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id></parent_id>



	<subject>Report on meeting with Comm. Bilas re GIR Proposed Decision</subject>



	<date_time>2000-12-08 04:48:00</date_time>



	<content>

    

M2.1. Alan,

[Conventional: salutation]

M2.2. here is a link to the Interim Settlement.

[Inform: link to Interim Settlement is presumably attached]

M2.3. Mike Day

[Conventional: signature]



	</content>

</message>

</xml>