<xml>

<message>



	<thread_id>20864</thread_id>



	<depth>0</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>1189976</message_id>

	<to name="Paul Simons" id="89569" address="paul.simons@enron.com"/>

	<from name="David Minns" id="2940" address="david.minns@enron.com"/>

	<cc name="Mark Taylor" id="2378" address="Mark.Taylor@ENRON.com"/>

	<cc name="Paul Quilkey" id="987" address="paul.quilkey@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id></parent_id>



	<subject>Guarantee from EEFT of Enron Australia Finance</subject>



	<date_time>2000-06-16 13:16:00</date_time>



	<content>

    

M1.1. Paul

[Conventional: salutation]

M1.2. further to my email/voicemail on our attempts to get an Exempt Market

Declaration issued to Enron Australia Finance Pty Ltd (EAF).

[Inform: this email is a follow-up to previous email and voicemail]

M1.3. I now have a

specific request to put to you.

[Inform: David has a request for Paul]

M1.4. It appears that we would qualify for such a  Declaration thereby allowing EAF

to use the safe harbour provisions under the Australian Corporations Law for

trading through EnronOnline if EAF had get a guarantee from  Enron Europe

Finance and Trading Ltd.

[Inform: it seems that David et al. qualify for an Exempt Market Declaration, allowing EAF to use safe harbor provisions for trading through EOL]

M1.5. We would be able to take advantage of a specific

provision in the policy guideline of the Australian Securities and

Investments Commission on the grant of Declarations known as Policy Statement

70.

[Inform: provision they can take advantage of is in Policy Statement 70]

M1.6. (Below is a summary of the relevant provisions of the Policy Statement.)

[Inform: summary of relevant provisions presumably attached]

M1.7. Would the provision of such a guarantee be possible?

[Request-Information: would provision of such a guarantee be possible]

Flink1.7

M1.8. Clearly an issue to consider would be any possible impact on EEFT's

prudential requirements under the Financial Services Act.

[Inform: possible impact on EEFT's prudential requirements needs to be considered]

M1.9. If this were an

issue perhaps could it be overcome if there was a back to back guaranty from

say Enron Corp. to EEFT.

[Inform: possible way to overcome such an impact]

M1.10. This mean that effectively EEFT would have no

additional exposure.

[Inform: in this case, EEFT would have no additional exposure]



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>20864</thread_id>



	<depth>1</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>1189998</message_id>

	<to name="Paul Simons" id="89569" address="paul.simons@enron.com"/>

	<from name="David Minns" id="2940" address="david.minns@enron.com"/>

	<cc name="Mark Taylor" id="2378" address="Mark.Taylor@ENRON.com"/>

	<cc name="Paul Quilkey" id="987" address="paul.quilkey@enron.com"/>

	<cc name="Alan Aronowitz" id="3611" address="Alan.Aronowitz@ENRON.com"/>



	<parent_id>1189976</parent_id>



	<subject>Guarantee from EEFT of Enron Australia Finance</subject>



	<date_time>2000-06-19 13:07:00</date_time>



	<content>

    

M2.1. Paul,

[Conventional: salutation]

M2.2. further to our discussion last Friday.

[Inform: this email is a follow-up to discussion in previous email]

M2.3. Attached is a complete copy of

Policy Statement 70 referenced in my earlier email.

[Inform: Policy Statement 70 attached]

M2.4. Paragraph PS70.50

contains the statement that authorisation under the SFA is considered to be

an adequate regime for monitoring capital adequacy.

[Inform: relevant paragraph pointed out]

M2.5. The SFA oversight  must

apply to either the entity that is trading under the Australian Exempt Market

Declaration as  or its guarantor.

[Inform: what SFA oversight must apply to]

M2.6. It is also in the this paragraph that the

reference to "low risk firms" is made.

[Inform: reference to "low risk firms" made in previously pointed out paragraph]

M2.7. Once you get a response to your enquiries we look forward to hearing whether

the provision of the guarantee is feasible.

[Inform: David et al. would like to know whether provision of guarantee is feasible after Paul's inquiries are responded to]



	</content>

</message>

</xml>