99492train
Annotation for intention:

Knowledge-Acquisition/Argumentation: Mertz' unwillingness to renew Erik's lease on a hunting lodge right away/Erik's and Brian's annoyance at this

Annotation for control:
Erik Wollam: Erik initiates the thread and tells the others about the problems he had with getting Mertz to sign his hunting lease.



<xml>

<message>



	<thread_id>99492</thread_id>



	<depth>0</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>285087</message_id>

	<to name="Brian Constantine" id="16942" address="brianc@saltgrass.com"/>

	<to name="Chris McComb" id="24008" address="cmccomb@austin-mccomb.com"/>

	<to name="Joe Parks" id="58825" address="Joe.Parks@ENRON.com"/>

	<to name="Keith McComb" id="67585" address="kmccomb@austin-mccomb.com"/>

	<to name="" id="57980" address="jmccomb@austin-mccomb.com"/>

	<to name="Chad Knipe" id="67782" address="knipe3@aol.com"/>

	<from name="Erik Wollam" id="39207" address="erwollam@hotmail.com"/>

	<to name="Joe Parks" id="58825" address="jparks@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id></parent_id>



	<subject>New Lease Update</subject>



	<date_time>2001-06-01 10:55:12</date_time>



	<content>

    

M1.1. Talked to Mertz last night.

[Inform: Erik talked to Mertz last night]

M1.2. Take this for whatever it is worth...

[Inform: recipients should take the following for what it's worth]

M1.3. Bottom line is that he says the lease I sent him, 16,000 per year for

2002

to 2005 looks good, it is the money he wants, we take good care of his

place, shoot mature bucks and we will get the lease, BUT he won't sign

the

lease until next fall, "because I don't have to". Whatever.

[Inform: Mertz says Erik et al. will get his requested lease, but not until next fall]

M1.4. I said we just wanted to know for certain that we had a place to hunt

for

the next four years and wanted to make sure we did not need to start

looking

for another lease.

[Inform: Erik expressed his concern to Mertz about having a place to hunt for the next four years]

M1.5. He said we had the place and not to worry about it,

he

just wanted to see how the new protien program panned out before signing



off.

[Inform: Mertz's excuse for not signing off on lease right away]

Sflink1.5

M1.6. Once again, whatever.

[Inform: expression of sarcastic indifference to Mertz's excuse]

M1.7. He also says he's pouring the stuff out heavy



right now.

[Inform: Mertz says he's pouring the stuff out heavy]

M1.8. He gave me his word and seemed upbeat about everything.

[Inform: Mertz made a promise and seemed optimistic]

M1.9. I'm going to

leave

it at that until next fall.

M1.10. I'm not going to worry about it anymore.

[Inform: Erik will not worry about the lease until next fall]

M1.11. His



great deal on the Zander's old lease fell apart on him (he was suppossed

to

have out of state hunters show up for two weeks and they were going to

pay

him 30k a year).

[Inform: a deal on an old lease that fell apart on Mertz]

M1.12. Maybe the concept of some good lessees who pay on time

and

take care of his land will look more realistic and attractive.

[Inform: Erik's opinion that he would be a better lessee than those whose plans fell through]

M1.13. He, as usual, stressed his never ending desire to grow a big deer. 

M1.14. He's

counting on this new super food to do it this year.

[Inform: Mertz has had a long-standing desire to acquire a big deer, and plans to do it this year]

M1.15. I guess the best we

can

do to assure a lease renewal is to hunt hard and kill him some big deer.

[Inform: Erik and recipients need to kill some big deer to ensure that Mertz renews their lease]



M1.16. Site in your guns and bring plenty of ammo next fall.

[Inform: recipients should sight their guns and bring a lot of ammunition next fall]

M1.17. Erik.

[Conventional: signature]



	</content>

</message>

<message>



	<thread_id>99492</thread_id>



	<depth>1</depth>



	<type>ThreadNode</type>



	<message_id>285060</message_id>

	<to name="Erik Wollam" id="39207" address="erwollam@hotmail.com"/>

	<to name="Chris McComb" id="24008" address="cmccomb@austin-mccomb.com"/>

	<to name="Joe Parks" id="58825" address="Joe.Parks@ENRON.com"/>

	<to name="Keith McComb" id="67585" address="kmccomb@austin-mccomb.com"/>

	<to name="" id="57980" address="jmccomb@austin-mccomb.com"/>

	<to name="Chad Knipe" id="67782" address="knipe3@aol.com"/>

	<from name="Brian Constantine" id="16942" address="brianc@saltgrass.com"/>

	<to name="Joe Parks" id="58825" address="jparks@enron.com"/>



	<parent_id>285087</parent_id>



	<subject>New Lease Update</subject>



	<date_time>2001-06-01 11:47:54</date_time>



	<content>

    

M2.1. RRRIIIIGGGGHHHHTTT....

[Inform: sarcastic response indicating strong skepticism]

Blink1.5



	</content>

</message>

</xml>

Hierarchical Power Annotation: N/A
Person_1: 
Person_2: 
Reason: 

Situational Power Annotation:
Person_1: Erik Wollam
Person_2: Brian Constantine, To(1)
Reason: Erik initiates the thread and tells the others about the problems he had with getting Mertz to sign his hunting lease.

Attempt at Exercising Power Annotation: N/A
DFUs: 
Person_1:
Person_2:
Type:
Successful?:
Reason: 

Influence Annotation:
Person_1: Erik Wollam
Person_2: Brian Constantine
Reason: Erik expresses his frustration with Mertz to the others, and Brian's sarcastic response to what Mertz said indicates he agrees with Erik.

Attempt at Influence Annotation:
DFUs: M1.3, M1.6, M1.12, M1.15-M1.16
Person_1: Erik Wollam
Person_2: Brian Constantine, To(1)
Successful?: Y
Reason: Erik expresses his frustration with Mertz to the others, and Brian's sarcastic response to what Mertz said indicates he agrees with Erik.
